SYED AIZAZ HASAN

253-F-Rehmanpura, Lahore | 03334663797 | hasanaizaz786@gmail.com

PROFILE

Sharp, top producing software engineer with over 2 year of professional experience. Providing programming and database expertise, with the intended to succeed in an environment of growth and excellence and earn a job which provides me a job satisfaction and self-development and to help me achieve personal as well as organizational goals. I have capability to prove efficiency in whatever held too I am assigned to and the ability to handle multiple task assignments and good knowledge of various data base systems and operating tool

EXPERIENCE

September, 2022 - Software Engineer, Sigma Square

Present

· Learn Node is to Implement middle-ware between 2 crms.

Learn And develop Wordpress plugins And themes.

develop custom Plugin of wordpress

Learn how to use node js in wordpress and make a middleware

between crm

Octuber, 2021-

Junior Software Engineer, Technology Castle

September,2022

· Learn to develop and manage Suitecrm

Manage Old Crm,s(develop new features and debug and maintain

old code, optimize the code). Manage Servers of Clients

Backend Development(customize crm according to clients requirement and provide assistance, backend development) Client Dealing(Daily Progress Report, conduct meetings, demo of

features)

Github(Creating repositories, managing all changes via github)

June,2021 -September,2021 Php Intern, Technology Castle

· Learn Php, Javascript, Ajax, Css, Laravel, HTML, Suitecrm, Apis

Learn basics of github Learn About Suitecrm

Learn About Servers and Linux

June,2019 -March,2020 Lab Manager, Peak Solutions College

Manage Students

September,2022- Software Engineer, Sigma Square

Present

· Learn Node js to Implement middle-ware between 2 crms.

Learn And develop Wordpress plugins And themes.

develop custom Plugin of wordpress

Learn how to use node js in wordpress and make a middleware

between crm

Keep all the Systems in check

troubleshoot any system that is not working

keep the software's up-to date

EDUCATION

2017-2021	Software Engineering, Lahore, Lahore Garrison University.
2015-2017	Intermediate in Computer Science, Lahore, Concordia College.
2010-2015	Matric(Computer Science), Lahore, Beacon House School System